Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art Board of Trustees records, 1869-2012 COR0001.0.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Early meeting records, 1869-1980; Series 1
  - Special Meeting, 1926 February 10; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Special Meeting, 1926 March 15; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1926 April 19; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Special Meeting, 1926 June 1; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1926 June 28; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Special Meeting, 1926 October 13; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1926 October 18; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Special Informal Meeting, 1926 December 19; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Annual Meeting, 1927; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1927 April 18; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Special Meeting, 1927 June 6; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1927 June 20; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1927 October 24; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Special Meeting, 1927 December 12; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Annual Meeting, 1928 January 16; Series 1 (Box 8, Folders 23-24)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1928 April 16; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Semi-Annual Meeting, 1928 June 11; Series 1 (Box 8, Folders 26-27)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1928 October 22; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Annual Meeting, 1929 January 21; Series 1 (Box 8, Folders 29-30)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1929 April 15; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1929 June 17; Series 1 (Box 8, Folders 32-33)
  - Quarterly Board Meeting, 1929 October 21; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Annual Meeting, 1930 January 20; Series 1 (Box 8, Folders 35-36)
  - (Advisory Committee) Special Meeting, 1930 February 24; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Special Meeting, 1930 March 6; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1930 April 21; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1930 June 16; Series 1 (Box 8, Folders 40-41)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1930 October 20; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Special Meeting, 1930 November 26; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Annual Meeting, 1931 January 19; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Special Meeting, 1931 January 19; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Special Meeting, 1931 March 19; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Special Meeting, 1931 April 9; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1931 April 29; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Special Meeting, 1931 May 15; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1931 June 15; Series 1 (Box 8, Folders 50-51)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1931 October 19; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Special Meeting, 1931 November 19; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Annual Meeting, 1932 January 18; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1932 June 20; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Special Meeting, 1932 July 13; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1932 October 17; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Special Meeting, 1932 December 1; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Special Meeting, 1932 December 14; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Annual Meeting, 1933 January 16; Series 1 (Box 10, Folders 4-5)
  - Adjourned Meeting, 1933 January 31; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1933 April 17; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1933 June 19; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Special Meeting, 1933 September 8, 12; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1933 October 16; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Annual Meeting, 1934 January 15; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1934 April 16; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1934 June 25; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Informal Conference, 1934 July 30; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Special Meeting, 1934 October 2; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1934 October 15; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Special Meeting, 1934 December 7; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Annual Meeting, 1935 January 21; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Special Meeting, 1935 February 4; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1935 April 22; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Special Meeting, 1935 May 3; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1935 June 17; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Special Meeting, 1935 July 17; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1935 October 21; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Special Meeting, 1935 December 26; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Annual Meeting, 1936 January 20; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Special Meeting, 1936 February 28; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1936 April 20; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1936 June 29; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Post-Poned Quarterly Meeting, 1936 October 26; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Special Meeting, 1936 December 17; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Annual Meeting, 1937 January 18; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Special Meeting, 1937 February 24; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1937 April 19; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Special Meeting, 1937 April 8; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Special Meeting, 1937 May 4; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1937 June 21; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Special Meeting, 1937 October 1; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1937 October18; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Special Meeting, 1937 November 15; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Special Meeting, 1937 December 14; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Annual Meeting, 1938 January 17; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1938 April 18; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1938 June 20; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1938 October 17; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Annual Meeting, 1939 January 16; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Special Meeting, 1939 March 30; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Semi-Annual Meeting, 1939 June 15; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1939 October 16; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1939 April 17; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Annual Meeting, 1940 January 19; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1940 April 19; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Semi-Annual, 1940 June 21; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1940 October 18; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Special Meeting, 1940 Nov 18; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Annual Meeting, 1941 Jan 17; Series 1 (Box 12, Folders 8-9)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1941 April 18; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Special Meeting, 1941 June 17; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Semi-Annual Meeting, 1941 June 20; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Special Meeting, 1941 September 18; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1941 October 17; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Special Meeting, 1941 December 11; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Annual Meeting, 1942 January 16; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Special Meeting, 1942 February 3; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Special Meeting, 1942 March 12; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1942 April 17; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Semi-Annual, 1942 June 19; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1942 October 23; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Annual Meeting, 1943 January 15; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1943 April 23; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Semi-Annual Meeting of Board, 1943 June 18; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1943 October 15; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Annual Meeting, 1944 January 28; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Special Meeting, 1944 March 6; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1944 April 21; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1944 June 23; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1944 October 20; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Annual Meeting, 1945 January 19; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Special Meeting, 1945 February 15; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1945 April 20; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Semi-Annual Meeting, 1945 June 15; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1945 October 19; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Annual Meeting, 1946 January 30; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1946 April 19; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Special Meeting, 1946 May 31; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Regular Quarterly Meeting, 1946 October 18; Series 1 (Box 12, Folders 39-40)
  - Annual Meeting, 1947 January 17; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Special Meeting, 1947 January 23; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Special Meeting, 1947 February 19; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Special Meeting, 1947 March 7; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1947 April 18; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Special Meeting, 1947 May 7; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Semi-Annual Meeting, 1947 June 19; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Quarterly Board Meeting, 1947 October 24; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Annual Meeting, 1948 January 23; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Regular Quarterly Meeting, 1948 April 16; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Semi-Annual Meeting, 1948 June 18; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Regular Quarterly Meeting, 1948 October 15; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Special Meeting, 1948 November 24; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Annual Meeting, 1949 January 24; Series 1 (Box 14, Folders 12-13)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1949 April 15; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Semi-Annual Meeting, 1949 June 17; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1949 October 21; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Special Board Meeting, 1949 November 4; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Special Board Meeting, 1949 November 30; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Special Board Meeting, 1950 January 11; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Annual Board Meeting, 1950 January 20; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Quarterly Board Meeting, 1950 April 21; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Semi-Annual Board Meeting, 1950 June 16; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Quarterly Board Meeting, 1950 October 20; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Special Board Meeting, 1950 December 6; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Annual Board Meeting, 1951 January 19; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Quarterly Board Meeting, 1951 April 20; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Semi-Annual Meeting, 1951 June 15; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Regular Quarterly, 1951 October 19; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Annual Board Meeting, 1952 January 18; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Regular Quarterly Meeting, 1952 April 18; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Semi-Annual Board Meeting, 1952 June 17; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Quarterly Board Meeting, 1952 October 17; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Annual Board Meeting, 1953 February 5; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1953 April 17; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Semi-Annual Board Meeting, 1953 June 19; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Regular Quarterly Meeting, 1953 October 16; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Annual Board Meeting, 1954 January 15; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Quarterly Board Meeting, 1954 April 21; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Semi-Annual Board Meeting, 1954 June 28; Series 1 (Box 15, Folders 3-4)
  - Regular Quarterly Meetings, 1954 October 25; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Annual Board Meeting, 1955 January 31; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Semi-Annual Meeting, 1955 June 27; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Regular Quarterly Meeting, 1955 April 25; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Regular Quarterly Meeting, 1955 October 31; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Annual Board Meeting, 1956 January 30; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Regular Quarterly Meeting, 1956 April 30; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Semi-Annual Board Meeting, 1956 June 25; Series 1 (Box 15, Folders 12-13)
  - Regular Quarterly Meeting, 1956 October 29; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Annual Meeting, 1957 February 6; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1957 April 17; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1957 July 15; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Regular Quarterly Meeting, 1957 October 28; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Annual Meeting, 1958 January 27; Series 1 (Box 15, Folders 19-20)
  - Regular Quarterly Meeting, 1958 April 25; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Semi-Annual Meeting, 1958 July 14; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Regular Quarterly Meeting, 1958 October 27; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Annual Meeting, 1959 January 26; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1959 April 27; Series 1 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Regular Quarterly Meeting, 1959 October 26; Series 1 (Box 15, Folders 26-27)
  - Annual Meeting, 1960 January 25; Series 1 (Box 15, Folders 28-29)
  - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1953 February 5-1957 July 15; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1957 October 28-1962 April 30; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1962 October 29-1967 May 1; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1967 October 30-1970 October 26; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Board of Governors, 1970-1972; Series 1 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1960 July 18; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Regular Quarterly Meeting, 1960 April 25; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Regular Quarterly Meeting, 1960 October 24; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Regular Quarterly Meeting, 1961 April 24; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Annual Meeting, 1961 January 30; Series 1 (Box 17, Folders 5-6)
  - Semi-Annual Meeting, 1961 June 17; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Regular Quarterly Meeting, 1961 October 30; Series 1 (Box 17, Folders 8-9)
  - [Annual Meeting], 1962 January 28; Series 1 (Box 17, Folders 10-11)
  - [Meeting], 1962 April 28; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - [Meeting], 1962 October 29; Series 1 (Box 17, Folders 13-14)
  - [Meeting], 1963 October 28; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - [Annual Meeting], 1963 January 28; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - [Meeting], 1963 April 29; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - [Meeting], 1963 October 28; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Annual Board Meeting, 1964 January 27; Series 1 (Box 17, Folders 19-20)
  - [Meeting], 1964 April 27; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - [Meeting], 1964 June 23; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - [Meeting], 1964 October 26; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Annual Board Meeting, 1965 January 25; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Annual Board Meeting, 1965 January 25; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - [Meeting], 1965 April 26; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - [Meeting], 1965 June 28; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Regular Quarterly Board Meeting, 1965 October 25; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Annual Meeting, 1966 February 7; Series 1 (Box 17, Folders 29-30)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1966 April 26; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1966 October 31; Series 1 (Box 17, Folders 32-33)
  - Annual Meeting, 1967 January 30; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Meeting, 1966 October 31; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Annual Meeting, 1967 January 30; Series 1 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - [Meeting Reports], 1967 October 30; Series 1 (Box 18, Folders 1-2)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1967 May 1; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Annual Meeting, 1968 January 22; Series 1 (Box 18, Folders 4-5)
  - [Meeting Reports], 1968 April 29; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - [Meeting Reports], 1968 May 27; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - [Meeting Reports], 1968 October 30; Series 1 (Box 18, Folders 8-9)
  - [Annual Meeting], 1969 January 27; Series 1 (Box 18, Folders 10-11)
  - [Meeting Reports], 1969 February 7; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - [Meeting Reports], 1969 April 28; Series 1 (Box 18, Folders 13-14)
  - [Meeting Reports], 1969 July 23; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - [Meeting Reports], 1969 October 27; Series 1 (Box 18, Folders 16-17)
  - [Annual Meeting Reports], 1970 January 27; Series 1 (Box 18, Folders 18-19)
  - [Meeting Reports], 1970 February 2; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - [Meeting Reports], 1970 April 27; Series 1 (Box 18, Folders 21-22)
  - [Meeting Reports], 1970 May 4; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - [Meeting Reports], 1970 October 26; Series 1 (Box 18, Folders 24-25)
  - Annual Meeting, Quarterly Reports, and Staff Manual, 1971 January 25; Series 1 (Box 18, Folders 26-28)
  - Trustee Meeting, 1971 April 26; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Various Depts., 1972; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - [Meeting Reports], 1973 March 19; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - [Meeting Reports], 1973 March 23; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - [Meeting Reports], 1973 September-October; Series 1 (Box 18, Folders 33-34)
  - [Meeting Reports], 1973 November-December; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - 1973 Reports, 1973 December 19; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Monthly Reports, 1974 January-February; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - [Meeting Reports], 1974 March-April; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Various Depts., 1974 May-June; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Monthly Reports and Directors Report, 1973 September 1-1974 August 31; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - [Meeting Reports], 1976 September; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - [Meeting Reports], 1978 August; Series 1 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1979 May 21; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1979 August 13; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1979 September 10; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1979 September 24; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1979 October 15; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1979 November 13; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1979 December 10; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1979 November 26; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Meeting, 1979 September 24; Series 1 (Box 24, Folders 9-10)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1980 January 14; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1980 January 28; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1980 February 11; Series 1 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1980 March 14; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1980 March 24; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1980 April 14; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1980 May 23; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1980 May 12; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1980 June 9; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1980 July 14; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Thom, Corcoran, Undated; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Thom, Corcoran, Undated; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Thom, Corcoran, Undated; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Thom, Corcoran, Undated; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Three Institutions Project Arena Stage, Corcoran, Folger Shakespeare Lib., 1980; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Three Institutions Project Arena Stage, Corcoran, Folger Shakespeare Lib., 1980; Series 1 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Records transferred post-1980, 1953-2012; 1979-2008; Series 2
  This series contains material generated by the Board of Trustees that was not included in the initial records transfer and processing of the Corcoran Archives in the 1980s. The records of the Board include Executive Committee Minutes, Trustee Reports, Board resolutions, correspondence, and Committee reports. Material dates from 1953-2012.
  - Photocopies of 1920s Trustees minutes and correspondence, 2008; Originals 1920s; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Existence and Location of Originals
    Original Meeting Minutes and correspondence in Series 1 Early meeting records, 1869-1980.
  - Photocopies of 1922-1926 Trustees minutes and correspondence, 2008; Originals 1922-1926; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Photocopies of 1917-1928 Trustees minutes and correspondence, 2008; Originals 1917-1928; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Photocopies of 1918-1921 Trustees minutes and correspondence, 2008; Originals 1918-1921; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Photocopies of 1922-1928 Trustees minutes and correspondence, 2008; Originals 1922-1928; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Photocopies of 1921-1928 Trustees minutes and correspondence, 2008; Originals 1921-1928; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Mission Statement, 1997; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Corcoran Strategic Plan, Undated; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - 2009 January 22, Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - [Executive Committee minutes], 2010 January, November, December; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Resolutions, Undated; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Conflict of Interest Statement, 2012; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Board Resolutions, 2009; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - September Board Retreat, 2007 September 17; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - 2007 November 19, Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - 2007 December 17, Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - 2008 January 28, Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Corcoran Creative Exchange, 2012 November; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Lobbyist Activites 2009, Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Liquor License, Undated; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Statement of Election to Accept Board of Trustees, Undated; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - American Association of Museums (AAM), 2004; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - American Association of Museums (AAM) Self Study, 2003; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - American Association of Museums (AAM), 2003; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - American Association of Museums (AAM), 1996; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - American Association of Museums (AAM), 2006; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - American Association of Museums (AAM) Self Study, 1994; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - American Association of Museums (AAM) Pre-1993, 1993 February; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Corcoran History, Undated; Series 2 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Art rental, sales desk reporters, Circa 1970; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee meeting minutes, 1975; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee meeting minutes, 1974 March 13; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee meeting minutes, 1974 May 15; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees By-laws, undated; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - letters to Aldus Chapin from Williams accompanying board meeting minutes (photocopies), 1960-1968; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee meeting, 1953-1961; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees meetings and special meeting materials (photocopies), 1977-1978; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Executive Committee meeting minutes [1/3], 1975-1978; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Executive Committee meeting minutes [2/3], 1975-1978; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Exective Committee meeting minutes [3/3], 1975-1978; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Executive Committee meeting minutes, 1974 September - December; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Executive Committee meeting minutes, 1973 July - December; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Executive Committee and Board of Trustees, 1958-1969; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Executive Commnittee meeting minutes, 1974-1975; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Executive Committee meeting minutes [1/2], 1975-1976; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Executive Committee meeting minutes [2/2], 1975-1976; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Executive Committee meeting minutes [1/2], 1976-1977; Series 2 (Box 20, Folder 18)